in a previous tutorial I demonstrated
在上一个教程中，我演示了
how you can use inkscape to create your
如何使用Inkscape创建您的
own Vector letters but in this tutorial
自己的矢量字母，但在本教程中
I'll be demonstrating how you can take
我将演示如何让你
those letters and turn them into a
并把它们变成一个
proper font file in ttf format so
TTF格式的正确字体文件，因此
getting us started here in inscape you
让我们在这里开始为你做准备
can see I have these simple letters that
可以看到我有这些简单的字母
I've designed if I grab my nodes tool
我设计了如果我抓住我的节点工具
and zoom in on this you can see how I
放大这个，你可以看到我是如何
created these these are just individual
创造了这些，这些只是个人的
paths that I apply to stroke to and I'm
我应用于笔划的路径，我是
going to use these letters to create a
我将使用这些字母来创建一个
font file uh for this demonstration so
用于此演示的字体文件，因此
in order turn these letters into a font
为了把这些字母变成一种字体
file we're going to need to download an
文件我们将需要下载一个
application called font uh font Forge
应用程序名为Font Uh Font Forge
it's a free and open- Source font editor
它是一个免费的开源字体编辑器
that allows you to create your own fonts
允许您创建自己的字体
as well so go ahead and download a font
同样，请继续下载字体
Forge from the link in the description
从描述中的链接伪造
launch the application and once you've
启动应用程序，一旦您完成
launched font Forge it should look
推出字体锻造它应该看起来
something like this so I'm going to
就像这样，所以我要
click on this button right here titled
点击此处标题为
new so I can create a new font and when
新建，以便我可以创建新字体以及何时创建
I do that we're going to get this window
我保证我们会得到这扇窗户
with all of these individual boxes in it
所有这些单独的盒子都在里面
and these boxes all represent the
这些方框都代表着
individual characters of the font your
您的字体的单个字符
creating so if you notice we have all of
如果你注意到我们有所有的
the special characters here we have the
这里的特殊人物我们有
numbers we have the uppercase letters
我们有大写字母的数字
the lowercase letters and some
小写字母和一些
additional special characters down here
此处有其他特殊字符
for this demonstration I'm just going to
在这个演示中，我只想
fill in the upper and lowercase letters
填写大小写字母
I'm going to go back into inkscape and
我要回到Inkscape，然后
to do this all we have to do is copy and
要做到这一点，我们所要做的就是复制和
paste each letter into each individual
将每个字母粘贴到每个单独的字母中
each individual box so I'm going to take
每个单独的盒子，所以我要拿着
the letter a right here I'll right click
字母a就在这里，我要右击
that and go to copy I'll come back over
然后去复印，我会回来的
here into font Forge and I'm going to
在这里进入Font Forge，我将
select the Box corresponding with the
选择对应的框
letter a and I'm just going to paste
字母a，然后我要粘贴
that in there either by right clicking
在那里可以通过右键单击
it and going to paste or you could just
然后粘贴，或者你可以直接
press contrl +v on the keyboard that
按键盘上的Ctrl+v组合键
paste that in there now if you notice in
如果你注意到了，现在就把它贴在那里
the thumbnail preview there the letter
那里的缩略图预览了这封信
is located in the top left of that
位于该项目的左上角
preview box there so we're going to
预览框在那里，所以我们要
adjust that by double clicking on the
通过双击
letter to open
要打开的信件
it and when we open it we're going to
当我们打开它的时候，我们会
get this editor here sort of like
把这个编辑叫到这里来，有点像
inkscape it allows you to change the
Inkscape它允许您更改
design if you'd like to it also allows
如果你喜欢设计，它还允许
you to change the position now the size
你现在要改变位置的大小
of your letter may vary depending on the
您的信件的日期可能会因
size of the letter in the software here
这里是软件中的字母大小
here if you find that your letter is too
在这里如果你发现你的信太
big or too small you can resize it
无论大小，您都可以调整大小
manually using the interface here or
手动使用此处的界面或
what I would recommend doing is going
我推荐的做法是去
back into inkscape and resizing all of
返回到Inkscape并调整所有
the letters at the same time so that
在同一时间的字母，以便
each letter is consistent when you
每个字母都是一致的，当你
create your font from it so uh if you
从它创建你的字体，所以呃，如果你
size these down one by one you're going
把这些东西一一缩小你要去的
to have inconsistent weights between the
之间具有不一致的权重
letters so I would recommend sizing them
所以我建议调整字母的大小
all at once my size here is pretty good
我的尺码一下子变得很好了
I'm going to leave it as it is what I am
我要让它成为我的本色
going to do though is I'm going to
不过，我要做的是
change the position of this letter if
如果出现以下情况，请更改此字母的位置
you notice down here this represents the
你注意到下面这张图代表了
Baseline of the text and this area down
文本的基线和此区域向下
here represents the area that goes
这里表示的是
beneath the Baseline so for example if
在基线下，例如如果
you were creating a lowercase G you
你在创造一个小写的G你
would want part of the letter to rest on
想要把信的一部分放在上面
the Baseline but you'd want that tail to
底线，但你会希望它的尾巴
dip down under there so to move this I'm
往下探，这样我就能移动它了
just going to click and drag over the
只需单击并拖动
letter here and I'm going to click and
字母在这里，我要点击并
drag one of these nodes and I'm going to
拖动其中一个节点，我将转到
hold the shift key and bring this down
按住Shift键并将其按下
until the node snaps onto the Baseline
直到节点捕捉到基线
and now you can see we have all of this
现在你可以看到我们拥有所有这些
extra space in here I'm going to close
这里有额外的空间，我要关闭了
that by taking this guide right here and
通过将这本指南带到这里并
just bringing this in further and I want
只是把这件事说得更深入一些，我想
to leave a little bit of space there
在那里留下一点空间
because this is going to repres repr the
因为这将代表
spacing between each letter so if I were
每个字母之间的间距，所以如果我是
to bring this all the way in there would
把这个一直带到那里就会
be no spacing between the letter a and
字母a和之间不能有空格
the next letter I type I want there to
我打出的下一封信我想在那里
be some spacing though so I'll put about
不过，要留点空隙，所以我会把
that much spacing in there and that
那里和那里有那么大的间距
looks pretty good I can close out of
看起来很不错，我可以结账了
that and now you can see the letter a is
现在你可以看到字母a是
all set so I'll repeat this process now
都准备好了，现在我要重复这个过程
with the letter B I'll just copy it by
有了字母B，我就把它抄下来
pressing contrl C come back in here come
按下Ctrl C键回到这里来
back in here press contrl V to paste it
回到这里，按Ctrl V粘贴它
double click the layer select the letter
双击层，选择字母
and grab the node and just snap this to
抓住节点，然后将其捕捉到
the bottom again holding shift to lock
底部再次按住Shift键锁定
it onto the vertical axis there we go
把它放到垂直轴上，我们走吧
now it snaps I can take this line and
现在它断了，我可以走这条线
move this
把这个搬开
in and close out of that and there we go
进进出出，我们就开始了
so what I'm going to do is I'll go
所以我要做的是我会去
through here and copy and paste all of
通过这里并复制和粘贴所有
these letters in here real quick and
这些字母在这里非常快和
I'll catch up with you when I'm
我到的时候会赶上你的
done so one minor thing I wanted to
做了一件我想做的小事
point out in regards to letters like a
就字母而言，如
lowercase G where the tail descends down
尾部向下的小写G
beneath the Baseline to move this letter
在基线下方移动此字母
we want to place the Baseline we want to
我们想要放置我们想要的基线
place this part of the letter right here
把信的这一部分放在这里
on the Baseline and we want this part of
在基线上，我们想要这部分
the letter to descend send beyond the
向下发送的信件超出了
Baseline so I'm going to select
基线，所以我将选择
everything and instead of clicking and
一切，而不是点击和
dragging the bottom node I'm going to
将底部节点拖到我要
take this node right here which is the
将这个节点放在这里，它是
node that I'd like to be on the Baseline
我想要在基线上的节点
and I'll drag it according to that one
我会根据那个拖拽它
again I'll hold shift and then snap that
我会再次按住Shift键，然后按下快门
node onto the Baseline and as you can
节点放到基线上，并尽可能
see there the letter G now descends
看那里，字母G现在下降了
beneath the Baseline as intended and I
如预期的那样位于基线下方，并且我
can move this line back in and we're
可以把这条线搬回来，我们
good to
太好了
go and for this particular font that I'm
对于我正在使用的这种特殊字体，
creating I don't have upper and
创造我没有鞋面和
lowercase variations of these letters I
这些字母的小写变体I
just have the lowercase varieties so I'm
只要有小写的变化，所以我
just going to copy and paste the
只需复制并粘贴
uppercase variety into the lowercase
大写字母变化为小写字母
boxes uh so that they're all the
盒子，呃，所以它们都是
same and once you're finished generating
同样的，一旦您完成生成
all of the characters for your font you
所有用于您的字体的字符
can give your font a name by coming up
我可以给你的字体起个名字
here to the element menu and choosing
转到元素菜单，然后选择
font info now this part's important
字体信息现在这部分很重要
because whatever you enter here is going
因为无论你在这里输入的是什么
to be the name of your font so if you
作为您的字体的名称，因此如果您
don't want your font to be named
我不希望您的字体被命名
Untitled one just go ahead and change
无名的就去换衣服吧
that to something else I'm just going to
那是我要做的其他事情
name this after myself I'll name it Nick
以我自己的名字命名，我会给它取名为尼克
and uh if if you want you could fill in
呃，如果你愿意的话，你可以帮我
this other metadata down here we have
下面我们有另一个元数据
all of this other stuff that you can
所有这些你能做的其他事情
look through if you'd like I'm just
如果你想看的话我只是
going to leave these defaults as they
将保留这些缺省值
are for this lesson and I'll click
是本课的内容，我将点击
okay and now to generate a font file I'm
好了，现在要生成一个字体文件，我
going to come up here to where it says
就会来到这里，上面写着
file and I'm going to select uh generate
文件，我将选择，呃，生成
fonts and from this menu you can choose
字体，您可以从此菜单中选择
where you would like to save your font
您想要保存字体的位置
file to you can use this dropdown to
文件，您可以使用此下拉菜单
choose the font file type I'm just going
选择我要使用的字体文件类型
to leave the default which is ttf and my
要保留缺省值TTF和My
font file is going to be called nick.
字体文件将被命名为Nick。
ttf and I'm just going to click generate
TTF和我只需点击生成
now when I click generate I'm going to
现在，当我单击生成时，我将执行以下操作
get these error messages because I
收到这些错误消息是因为我
didn't create a proper font file there's
没有创建正确的字体文件
a lot of errors with what I created here
我在这里创建的内容有很多错误
I'm just going to skip past this I'm
我就跳过这一步我要
going to click
要点击
generate and if you open up your files
生成文件，如果您打开文件
I'm going to open this right here you
我要把这个打开，就在这里，你
can see nick. ttf there is my font and
可以看到尼克。TTF那里有我的字体和
there is the preview of the font that I
这是我使用的字体的预览
created and I'll go ahead and install
已创建，我将继续并安装
this and now this font can be used
现在可以使用这种字体
virtually anywhere in your operating
在您的运营过程中几乎在任何地方
system not just with inkscape with any
系统不仅具有Inkscape，还具有任何
design app that you want any word
设计你想要的任何单词的应用程序
processor in fact I'll reload inkscape
处理器事实上，我将重新加载Inkscape
here just to show you what I mean let me
在这里向你展示我的意思让我
close out of this and relaunch the
关闭这个，并重新启动
software let me shrink that
软件可以让我缩小它
down and I'll just write in some
向下，我只会写一些
placeholder text I'll press contr a to
占位符文本我将按Ctrr a以
select it all and I'm going to go
全选好了，我要走了
looking for my font here in this list so
在此列表中查找我的字体，因此
I'm looking for
我在找
Nick there it is I'll click apply and
尼克，这就是了，我将点击应用，然后
there is the font that I've created and
这是我创建的字体和
in fact I can go and change this now you
事实上，我可以去改变这一切，现在你
know what let me try that
知道什么能让我试一试吗
again
再来一次
and if I bring out let me let me open
如果我拿出来，让我打开
the rulers by pressing controlr and I'll
按CONTROR键打开尺子，我就会
bring down a horizontal guide if I place
如果我放置水平参考线，则将其取下
this horizontal guide here you could see
这里的水平参考线，你可以看到
what I was talking about earlier with
我之前谈到的是
the uh the Baseline of the text the
文本的基线
Baseline sits the letters all sit on the
基线坐着字母都坐在
proper Baseline and the letter G and the
正确的基线和字母G以及
letter Y descend beneath it the same
字母Y在其下方的位置相同
with the letter P as well so that is how
还有字母P，所以这就是为什么
you can go about creating your own font
您可以着手创建自己的字体
files using Vector elements if you found
使用向量元素的文件(如果找到
this lesson useful then consider
这一课很有用，然后考虑
checking out my inkscape master class
查看我的Inkscape大师课
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where I go over all of the tools and
在那里我检查了所有的工具和
features in inkscape and I explain what
Inkscape中的功能，我将向您解释
they are and demonstrate how they work
它们是并演示了它们的工作方式
kind of like how I did in this video we
有点像我在这段视频中所做的
even have a private Community where you
甚至拥有一个私人社区，在那里你可以
can ask questions and get help from me
可以问我问题并得到我的帮助
anytime you want and best of all there's
任何你想要的时间，最好的是有
no monthly membership fees you just pay
你只需支付月费就可以了
$17 one time and you're in for Life I'll
一次17美元，你就会被判终身监禁
have some information about that down
我有一些关于这方面的信息
below if you want to check that out as
如果您想要将其查看为
always thanks for
永远感谢你
watching
观看
[Music]
[音乐]
h
H